A U D R E Y N G U Y E N

Visual Communications & Design

5435 Copper Springs Lane Cumming, GA 30040

678 - 335 - 6818

□ audreytnguy@gmail.com

https://audrey-nguyen.github.io/portfolio/

PROFILE

My art practice includes a variety of media however, my main focus is in visual communications. I am interested in graphic, web and product design. Additionally, I've become more curious about the user interface and motions with graphics as it relates to the digital experience for consumers.

EXPERIENCE

Double Trip Press

January 2020 - Present | *Independent Contractor* August 2019 - December 2019 | *Intern*

 Assisted in day to day studio activities including pre-press setup, letterpress printing, post-press production, and assembly of works.

SAIC Media Center

February 2019 - Present | Equipment Facilitator

Operated the checkout system to circulate equipment while providing customer service to students, faculty, and staff.

Orientation Staff

Aug. 2019 - Sep. 2019 | Senior OL & Orientation Leader Introduced new students to the academic, intellectual, cultural, and social environment of SAIC and Assisted with the implementation of Orientation sessions and activities.

Rambo Nursery

May 2019 - August 2019 | Plant Merchandiser

Maintained products on shelves including water management, proper spacing, and visual display while keeping a clean environment.

SAIC Admissions Office

August 2018 - May 2019 | Phone Caller

Made phone calls to prospective students encouraging them to attend school events and answered any questions or concerns that they had.

EDUCATION

Undergraduate Junior graduating May 2022 with a BFA and emphasis in Visual Communications.

• Merit Scholarship Recipient, 2018 — 2022

RECOGNITIONS

ArtBash

2019 | Faculty Select

Was selected by faculty to have work featured in SAIC's ArtBash exhibition.

All-State Art Symposium

2018 | 1st Place

Scholastics Art and Writing Award

2018 | Silver Key 2017 | Honorable Mention

Governor's Honor Program

2017 | Finalist

Participated in a state funded summer program as a Visual Arts major and Science minor while residing at Berry College. Did various activities that provided challenging and enriching educational opportunities.

SKILLS

Software

Illustrator, InDesign, Photoshop, Adobe XD, Lightroom, After Effects, Premier Pro, Rhino, Arduino, P5js, Fritzing

Machine

3D printer, Laser cutter, Plotter cutter, CNC (Othermill)

Communication

Customer Service, Teamwork, Visual merchandising

COMMUNITY INVOLVEMENT

Art and Chill Club

2018 - 2020 | Member

Dungeons and Dragons Club

2018 - 2020 | Officer